[Music]
[Música]
Okay family so let's give it one
bueno familiar pues vamos a darle al
last click of the night then I'm going to
último clic de la noche luego me voy a
dinner when I finish this clip
cenar cuando termine este clip
and I'll come back in half an hour I'll
y vuelvo a la media hora
go to dinner and have a drink for an hour half an
iré a cenar ya tomar algo una horita
hour an hour break ok and we'll
media horita una horita descanso vale y
come back with hard training ok in
volvemos con entrenamiento duro vale por
case anyone doesn't know I'm going to put it
si alguien no lo sabe lo voy a poner
here to dyn
aquí a dyn
gameplays
gameplays
in case anyone doesn't know
por si alguien no lo sabe
this Monday is Valentine's Day
este lunes de san valentín
[Music]
[Música]
Forni te Valentine duets with someone play
forni te valentine dúos con alguien play
okay this Monday we're in another tournament
vale este lunes estamos en otro torneo
this Monday we're in another tournament let's see
este lunes estamos en otro torneo a ver
what I think there was another video around here
que creo por aquí había otro vídeo
guys the season of romance
chicos arranca la temporada del romance
and shooting starts because together with this rival
y los disparos porque junto a este rival
we're going to have a Valentine's Day event
vamos a tener un evento de san valentín
[Music]
[Música]
so as not to be the last time Javi
hace por no ser la última vez javi le
tells him in blue that they supposedly
dice en azul que supuestamente
mentioned both of them for the tournament
le mencionaron a ambos para el torneo el
Ari's string from a while ago send me
string de ari de hace un rato mandarme
the clip send me the click but if
el clip mandarme el click pero si
we are the south and I are romantic couples
estamos el sur y yo somos parejas
the south and I are romantic couples in
el sur y yo somos parejas románticas en
this tournament okay me with the south my partner
este torneo vale yo con el sur mi pareja
is the south
es el sur
or store creators will face each other in a
o tienda creadores se enfrentarán en un
rapid until they lose in shape and for  a
rápido hasta perder en forma y por un
very very special prize of 25 thousand
premio muy muy especial de 25 mil
dollars that will be distributed among all
dólares que será repartido entre todos
are participations like juanes de
son participaciones como juanes de
guarnizo mixed without family the one to
guarnizo mixtas sin familia el de
extend and more
extender y más
[Music] let's
[Música]
see how long it lasted in this tournament who
a ver cuánto duró en este torneo quien
is in the tournament because I don't know I don't know I don't
hay en el torneo por no lo sé no sé no
know if he will have said it today I would look at it you
sé si lo habrá dicho hoy haría mirar la
see if he said it well then we do
veis si lo ha dicho pues hacemos luego
a click or the participants
un clic o los participantes
if he said it ari let's see
si lo ha dicho ari a ver
[Music]
[Música]
search for me there
buscar melo
are 80 80
son 80 80
it would be done what you made a t-
estaría hecho lo que hicieras una
shirt with your surfing career I don't know I do
playera con tu carrera del surf
n't know hunger still if it will be I
no sé no sé hambre aún si estará me
imagine
imagino
80 participants but of course there are 40
80 participantes pero claro son 40
couples girls balls they are
parejas chicas un [__]
many it
son muchos
's one day one day there are already many there are
es un día un día ya son muchos
40 couples
40 pareja
yes here in year
si aquí en año
what people
qué gente
and download for nobody on the pc I'm not going to
y descargar por nadie en el pc no voy a
play the play
jugar la play
then now at night we play okay now
luego ahora por la noche jugamos vale
after the break we're going to practice for
después del descanso vamos a practicar
a while okay it still hasn't exploded on me with his
un rato vale aún no me explota con su
chat for this why why exploded
chat por esto por qué por qué explotado
euro classroom always explodes it is pure
aula euro siempre explota es es pura
dynamite it
dinamita
leaks when he starts smoking again again again
se filtra cuando se pone a fumar
the old man you know  the
otra vez otra vez el viejo sabes a la
camera was on while smoking
cámara encendía fumando
it has leaked when he started
se ha filtrado cuando ahora se puso a
smoking in his live yesterday well it happens
fumar en su directo de ayer pues sucede
that he wanted to change the scene and by
que este quería cambiar de escena y por
mistake you can see when he takes out his
error se ve cuando éste saca sus
cigarettes before going to the bathroom this
cigarros antes de irse al baño esto
happened because he accidentally put
sucedió debido a que sin querer puso a
the skil scene of the gay skin instead of removing the bed I'm going to look at the legal age slim dare you sometime leave oh well I already sent you a dm to see quiet acts or just for that photo of acts in tweet I'm going to look at the age to see is
en tweet voy a mirar a la edad a ver es
that they give us a diet see it
que nos den dieta ve
's not a child smoking don't be a
no es un niño fumando no seas una
34 year old person no
persona de 34 años no
if it were a child he doesn't have a child
si fuera un niño no tiene un niño
smoking I don't know what well it
fumando no sé qué
scandalizes you no but a man
pues te escandaliza no pero un hombre
smoking well is a man smoking who
fumando bueno es un hombre fumando que
tries not to show it trying to
lo intenta no mostrar intentado
hide it if he tries but not for nothing
ocultarlo si intenta pero no por nada
but because it
sino porque
looks prettier in a street where he doesn't
queda más bonito en un street que no
smoke he doesn't try so that it can't be seen in his
fumes no intenta que no se vea en sus
live shows that he smokes he quit the cigarette that I do
directos que el fuma dejó el cigarro que
n't know what
no sé qué
Carlos V doing outside a child that
carlos v haciendo fuera un niño que
wolves smoking our
lobos fumando al nuestro
Auro gets quite angry with the chat
auro se enfada bastante con el chat
the photo is arranged  at the same time with me we have to
la foto la dispuestos a la vez conmigo
fix the scene air we have to
hay que arreglar la escena aire hay que
fix it auron ends up getting angry
arreglarla auron termina enfadándose
when he sees that he is already heavy with
cuando ve que él ya está pesado con
comments like euro in form don't smoke
comentarios tipo euro en forma no fumes
because you don't smoke not because in you smoke and
porque no fumas no porque en fumas y
explodes saying the chop
explota diciendo el chop
opportunity to creators and new ones
oportunidad a creadores y nuevos
totally agree I think it's
totalmente de acuerdo creo que es una
something that there have been many series in which
cosa que ha habido muchas series en la
this has happened me not only have
que esto ha pasado yo no solamente
you not been wrong you have not
os habéis equivocado no
been wrong opportunity to
os habéis equivocado oportunidad a
creators if it's going to happen click on and
creadores si va a pasar clic en y
there the click happens in that idea we
ahí pasa el clic en esa idea
wanted to see gross exploding that I
queríamos ver a gross explotando que
can see what the fuss way that has to do
puedo ver qué pedo way que tiene que ver
with this
en esto
while the rules let's see what
mientras que las reglas vamos a ver qué
happened
ha pasado
I wouldn't go with any of a
no me iría con ninguno de un canal de
gossip channel most of me like that
chismes la mayoría me cae bien que se
the secret is kept and then they tell you
guarda el secreto y luego te lo cuentan
with them where I already have my
con ellos donde ya tengo mi
plan to see if the streaming is turned off and I
plan a ver si se apaga el streaming y me
go
voy
[Laughs]
[Risas]
but the fact is that where they want it
pero hecho que a donde lo quieren
with me
conmigo
[ __ ] the mother
[__] la mother
is the click where he smokes
es el clic donde fuma
ah okay but there was another click where he
ah vale pero había otro click donde
exploded
explotaba no
you have not been wrong
os habéis equivocado
okay okay more they sell joking
vale vale más venden bromeando
today guys now let's go to
hoy chicos ahora vamos a
[Music]
[Música]
now let's practice the game okay
ahora vamos a practicar el juego vale
when I get back from break but be
cuando vuelva del descanso pero
quiet, silence okay
calladitos el silencio vale
because I'm already that my throat can't even
que ya estoy que la garganta no puedo ni
speak
hablar
friends thanks for being here one more day I'm
amigos gracias por estar aquí un día más
going to look at the legal age slim
voy a mirar a la edad legal slim
dare to leave sometime
atrévete alguna vez dejarte
and I've
y
already sent you a dm to see if you're a
ya te he enviado un dm a ver acaso ser
liar just for that photo of axel on
mentiroso sólo por eso foto de axel en
twitter at this moment in which friends I'm
twitter en este momento en el que amigos
going to give you some information okay I'm going to give you
os voy a dar un dato vale os voy a dar
some information that I think is important to
un dato que creo que es importante
know okay I'm 33 years old I don't want to
saberlo vale tengo 33 años no me quiero
smoke a cigarette or I want to smoke 7 I
fumar un cigarro o me quiero fumar 7 me
smoke them in fact I put them in my ass I mean
los fumo es más me los meto en el culo
expensive if I were five or twelve I would
o sea caro si tuviera cinco años o doce
understand if people told me damn it's
entendería que la gente me dijera ostia
not good it's not right what you're
no es bueno no está bien lo que estás
doing I'm 33 years old friends of
haciendo tengo 33 años amigos por
course I put cigarettes even
supuesto que me meto los cigarros hasta
in my ass of course be please it's that
en el culo claro sea por favor
I freak out that the one with the lock and I
es que yo flipo que la de ese candado y
know with that that
se con eso
I freak out man but every time I
el que yo flipo tío pero cada vez le
passed the elo abidine it's like once
pasaba la elo abidine es como una vez
they try to hide it because it looks
ellos lo intentan ocultar porque queda
nicer that you can't see the
como más bonito que no se te ve el
cigarette in the 21st such but that  if it should be
cigarro en el xxi tal pero que si se
done unintentionally or whatever it is that
debe hacer sin querer o lo que sea que
you smoke smoking affects children and adults you
tú fumes fumar afecta a niños y adultos
already know but well, it's
ya idea pero bueno
not very good that they scold him it
pues no está muy bien que le echen la
's very good that they scold him
bronca está muy bien que le echen la
for smoking well yes as adults
bronca por fumar pues sí como ya adultos
like me it's that nonsense of
como yo es que qué tonterías por
course I mean the thing is that there comes a
supuesto o sea es que es que llega un
time when you say damn let's see what it is that I'm
momento que dices [__] a ver qué es que
33 years old well it doesn't matter you have to
tengo 33 años pues no da igual lo tienes
quit damn
que dejar [__]
I've been doing it for three months now no family when
yo llevo ya tres meses no familia cuando
I've been doing it what's up the mites if I had I'll
llevo yo que pasa los ácaros si tuviera
tell you your second plane yesterday he
ya te digo tu segundo plano ayer me
sent me a clip of Joan Plana that
mandar un clip de joan plana
was really good god I don't know how we didn't have
buenísimo dio no sé cómo no teníamos
this clip someone didn't pour
este clip alguien no vertió
in one of so many others meanwhile no
en uno de tanto otro más entretanto no
but very good this critic
pero buenísimo el crítico este
listen to it
escucharlo
the pear has it
la pera
well the other browser because
lo tenga bien el otro navegador porque
if I don't want to be
si no quiero ser
very good he is a
buenísimo es crítico
very good critic man
buenísimo tío
he
él
is talking about HIV and says
está hablando del vih y dice
that HIV is victimizing himself no that as he
qué vih se victimiza no que como él lo
has dismantled it also
ha desmontado también
how do we do now so that his criticisms
como hacemos ahora para que sus críticas
are not valid we
no sea válida
cannot answer because he is right we
no podemos contestar porque tiene razón
have no arguments to contrast
no tenemos argumentos para contrastar
how is it not going to correct because the body
como no va a corregir porque el cuerpo
puts that conclusion on itself that  it's
esa conclusión se pone de sí que es
harassment, what abuse, what an obsession these people go and
acoso que abuso qué obsesión estos van y
with this the track is removed above and 25
con esto se quita la pista encima y 25
personal and with this it is removed man
personal y con esto se quita tío es
this click is brutal
brutal este clic
[Music]
[Música]
with
con
the
la gente
main people is
principal es
brutal describing what the siege
brutal el describiendo lo que el asedio
12 13 14 15 and cesc damn what does that
12 13 14 15 y cesc [__] qué hace esa
person do with his life no friends of
persona con su vida no amigos por
course I smoke I've been doing it for years
supuesto que fumo llevo años haciéndolo
and I'm going to continue doing it and every
y lo voy a seguir haciendo y cada
cigarette I put it in my ass that nothing is
cigarro me lo meto en el culo que nada
boring that you don't smoke damn every cigarette
fome que no se fuma [__] cada cigarro
you smoke is hurting yourself
que te fumes es hacerte daño
for free and without the need of the body
gratuitamente y sin necesidad del cuerpo
mature please mature I ask for that
maduren por favor maduren os pido esa
great maturity that is ridiculous it is already a
gran madurez que es el ridículo ya es
burden of shame I feel ashamed
que lastra vergüenza siento vergüenza
when these things happen
cuando pasan estas cosas
[Music]
[Música]
how can you be such an [ __ ]
como se puede ser tan [__]
you have discovered America I have
has descubierto américa
old videos smoking from
tengo vídeos antiguos fumando del año
2013 and 2014 I have videos where I made a
2013 y 2014 tengo vídeos donde hacía un
blog and I smoked a cigarette so
blog y me fumaba un cigarro así que
now I don't do it I think it's ugly I think it's
ahora no lo hago me creo que está feo
worse and of course more than
creo que está peor y por supuesto más de
once I go to the bathroom and while  I pee I
una vez voy al baño y mientras meo me
smoke a little cigarette and I relax and it feels really
fumo un cigarrito y me relajo y me queda
good and it feels really good and
a gustísimo y me queda a gustísimo ya
sometimes it takes me a while because I'm smoking a little
veces tardo porque me estoy fumando un
cigarette calming down I relax I read
cigarrito calmando me tranquilo leo
twitter what's happening I'm 33 years old
twitter que pasa que tengo 33 años
friends please it's
amigos por favor
really absurd some
es que de verdad es absurdo algunas
people don't smoke obviously I
personas no fuméis evidentemente eso sí
have to say that it's not right but
que lo tengo que decir no está bien pero
I do do it and that's it hey I'm glad that
yo sí lo hago y ya está oye yo me alegro
you guys regrettable now
de que vosotros lamentable ahora
regrettable you guys in fact I don't advise it it's
lamentable hayáis es más no lo aconsejo
something that is poison it's wrong but
es algo que es veneno está mal pero
hey I decide what I put in my
bueno yo decido lo que me meto en el
body and what I don't really but gosh
cuerpo y lo que no la verdad pero vaya
you know but don't do it
tú sabrá pero no lo hagas
I appreciate all those people who
agradezco a toda esa gente que se
care but there's no need to
preocupa pero no hace falta que te
worry about a 33 year old man
preocupes por un señor de 33 años de
really no well yes because 33 years old is very
verdad no pues sí porque 33 años es muy
young and 33 years old is very young and you have to
joven y 33 años muy joven y te tienes
take care of yourself as much as possible your greetings
que cuidar el máximo posible tu saludo
I thought to stop smoking that I
yo pensé para quitarme de fumar que
often quit I quit
muchas veces lo dejaba yo lo dejé
because I quit before getting sick the
por lo dejé antes de ponerme malo lo
bad
malo
and I went two or three years without smoking and  he was
y estuve dos o tres años sin fumar y
falling again with the confinement with
volvía a caer con el confinamiento con
the confinement it's normal but now he's stopped
el encierro es normal pero ahora le deja
again and I don't know if three months without smoking
otra vez y no sé si tres meses sin fumar
or you don't know, let's say and it wasn't much
o no lo sabéis vamos y ya no fue mucho
anyway but
de todas maneras pero
I think that what I
yo creo que yo lo que lo que yo me
mentally thought about seemed like eight very well h puto
mentalizo parecían ocho muy bien h [__]
mother well I'm 36 years old
madre bueno tengo 36 años
the more I take care of myself the better I'll be
cuanto más me cuide mejor voy a estar
when I'm 46 and I'll be better when I
cuando sea 46 y mejor voy a estar cuando
'm 56 and better until 486 the
tenga 56 y mejor hasta 486 cuanto más
younger the body one the body can't
chico el cuerpo uno el cuerpo no lo
replace it okay but if he wants to
puede sustituir vale pero si él quiere
smoke because he smokes
fumar porque fume
the thing is that people don't get
la cosa es que la gente no se
scandalized or that he smokes that he smokes that he smokes it's
escandalice o que fuma que fuma que fuma
channeling no but if he's putting
es canalizarse no pero si está poniendo
people not smoking anymore it wasn't for that he smokes I do
la gente ya no fume no fue para que fuma
n't know what position it's fine because they
no sé qué puesto está bien porque se
are worrying about his health and nothing
están preocupando por su salud y nada
family well up to here a moment is worth it to us
familiar pues hasta aquí momento nos
a moment is worth it
un momento lo vale
[Music]
[Música]